为什么现在看起来如此华丽我为什么不能进入三角形
Why can't I get into triangles when I look so gorgeous it now
关于那个角度
Angles about that
之前的西瓜
A watermelon before
Penny Mordaunt
天然巫婆刀见你
Natural witch knife see you
宜家时钟
IKEA clocks
到场
Turn up
耶稣基督
Jesus Christ
我这听起来像手术的声音
I have a feeling this is what surgery sounds like
剖腹产
C-section
像演员直线一样玩不太清楚
Play like an actor straight line not quite sure what
听到
To hear
这是怎么回事
What is this way
确实有效
Does actually work
就是这样
That's that
我真的可以知道我在做什么吗
Can I really know what I'm doing
快醒来
Wake up now
我有这个西瓜
I got this watermelon
所以现在我要
So now I'm going to
再次
Again
我不喜欢这样
I don't like this
玩三角
Play The Triangle
我的头部但仍然开放
My brain surgery but still open
有人会看着我这样做，如果我做对了或者我做错了
Somebody is going to watch me do this and if I do this right or if I do this wrong
并说
And say
没有
No
设计
Design
我只用刀子简单简单的厨师刀
I just go with the knife simple simple chef knife
这样，它就可以稳定在您的木板上，割伤自己或伤害自己
This way it's steady on your board and cut yourself or hurt yourself
我知道我在做什么我就在这里
I know what I'm doing I'm just in here
直下一分钟
Straight down a minute
扭转局面
Turn it around
好，然后我们可以
Ok and then we can
从2:30
From 2:30 quarters
好
Ok
阿迪达斯中心步道超级超级简单
Adidas centre trails super super simple
Anatole可以使西瓜完美吗
Anatole can a watermelon perfect
这是
This is
平行四边形
Parallelogram
我们可以把它变成一个三角形
We can make it into a triangle
痴迷美学
Obsessed with aesthetics